#8 "It's Not You"
95, 96, 97...
98, 99, 100.
All right. Every fiber of muscle,
from my transverse abdominal muscles
to my rectus abdominis muscles, is fat-free.
That must be Master.
Wh-Wh-What's going on?
Incoming Call
Adagaki Aki
Adagaki... That Adagaki Aki is calling me?
I never even fathomed that
something like this would happen.
Talk about a bolt from the blue!
Like pulling a muscle right
at the starting line!
Should I at least answer it?
Wait, but this might be some kind of trap.
A way to build me up,
only to push me down into Hell!
Incoming Call
Adagaki Aki
I'm just going to go for it!
Hello?
Answer faster!
Luggage from the island trip?
Yeah. Apparently I forgot one of my bags.
And she wants to give it
to me in person tomorrow.
Surprising, isn't it?
That Adagaki would say something like that.
Just like you said, maybe the
plan on the island went well.
Pig's Foot, you should think
about this more carefully.
Huh?
This is definitely a huge step,
but if you make even one mistake,
we don't know what will happen.
Man... Master could have
been a bit happier for me.
Well, I guess I'll do my homework.
Huh?
What? Huh?
What's going on?!
The picture's gone!
Back then...
That woman...
Hey, thanks.
How careless can you be,
to leave your things at my villa?
R-Right... I'm glad you came
to return it to me in person.
I would've preferred to send it
to you. But Yuisaki-san said...
Huh?
What? You're going out, but you're
going to have it delivered to him?
She started making strange inquiries.
Props to the hot secretary!
What?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Listen well, Makabe.
If you continue to act overly
familiar with me, you'll be sorry.
That face...
It hasn't changed at all from eight years ago.
Come to think of it,
the one who stole that picture
was probably Fujinomiya Neko.
I can only imagine that
she swiped it back then.
She should be able to tell right away that
the girl in the picture is Adagaki Aki.
She might even be able to tell that the
boy is the Pig's Foot version of me.
By the way, Makabe, have
you heard from Futaba-san?
She asked if we'd all like to
go to the pool tomorrow.
We just got back from the villa.
I think it's way too soon.
Yeah...
I don't get it.
Why would she just take
it and not say anything?
You'd think anyone would have
some questions about it.
Makabe.
Doesn't it bug her?
Makabe, are you listening?
Why would she even take it, then?
Makabe!
Wh-What's the matter, Adagaki-san?
If it's such a bother to talk to me,
I'd be more than happy
to leave, as you wish.
No, I'm sorry, I...
Good day!
Thank you very much.
Mommy, did that guy just get dumped?
Shh!
After all she just ate... That little...
What am I doing?
This is exactly what
Master was talking about.
Leaving things how they are right
now is probably not a good idea.
Incoming Call
Fujinomiya Neko
Hello?
Oh, is this Masamune-sama?
This is Neko. Do you have a moment?
Y-Yeah. What's up?
Yes, well, Futaba-san had
invited me to go to the pool,
but I was wondering if you were
going as well, Masamune-sama.
I see.
U-Um...
Actually, what are you doing right now?
Right now, I'm currently alone in my room.
Do you think we could meet up right now?
What?
No, not in a weird way or anything...
I would be happy to! Then...
Welcome, Masamune-sama.
Th-Thanks...
Please, come in.
I regret that I don't have much to offer.
My first time being inside a girl's house...
No, if I include Adagaki Aki's
house, this would be the second.
But that doesn't count!
So this is what they call
going to a girl's place!
Masamune-sama?
Nothing ventured, nothing gained!
If I want to find out the
truth about the photo,
I have to become the moth that
dives directly into the flame!
Go, Masamune! Be a man!
Pardon the intrusion.
I'll put on some tea.
This is quite an apartment.
Are you living with your attendant?
Yes. This is a secondary residence that my
father and grandfather use for work.
This was the only place they would allow.
What brought you here so suddenly?
I am very happy to see you, but...
I forgot to think up a reason.
Um...
Well, I just happened to be in the area...
That's painful. That excuse
is insanely painful.
My, it must have been fate. How wonderful.
Is she seriously happy? Seriously?
Ugh! The more I think about it,
the more I have no idea what's going on!
Say, Fujinomiya-san,
I know this is sudden,
but can I use your bathroom?
Yes. It's at the end of the hall.
Thanks.
First, I need to determine
whether the picture is really here.
I need to find out exactly
who I'm dealing with.
I feel bad about going in
without permission, but...
Is this her room?
I can't be intimidated
by a girl's room forever!
Ow... What the heck?
Vitamin
Yeah, no matter how I look
at it, this is Neko-sama's room.
It's a lot messier than I expected.
Romance stuff?
Is she into S&M?
Is she gonna tie me up?!
And now "Rose-eyed Steroid"?
I don't get her at all anymore.
The tea's ready.
Was the bathroom too hard to find?
N-No, not at all.
Oh, that's "Rose-eyed Steroid"!
Isn't it lovely?
After I spotted it in your room,
I became curious and had
Shidou purchase them.
I've read volume three so many times!
She just admitted to sneaking into my room.
That scene on the roof was just...
Fujinomiya-san, can I ask you a question?
Yes. What is it?
When you came to my house the other day,
did you take a photo from my room?
So you've found me out.
That is unfortunate.
What were you thinking? Why?
I knew it was wrong...
Where the hell were you hiding that thing?!
But it was such a cute picture,
I couldn't help myself.
C-Cute? You mean Adagaki?
You must be joking.
I mean you, Masamune-sama.
I'm cute?
You were truly adorable. You look
like that fellow, Kintarou-san.
But I was fat.
And what is wrong with that?
You actually think that?
Crap. This isn't good.
That hit me harder than I thought.
I might actually cry.
Yes. I'm very envious of Aki-sama,
since you think so highly of her.
So this is how soft a girl's lips are...
One's appearance is but a
single aspect of that person.
One's health comes first.
If Shidou-san finds us, we'll be in trouble.
She has work at the main house
today and will be away all day.
None of this matters anymore.
If being a fatty or a hottie
just makes up a "single aspect,"
none of it matters.
My ambitions and revenge
don't matter.
I won't fall for you.
You're just a Pig's Foot!
Masamune-sama?
Fujinomiya-san, do you know how
to get home when your shoes
aren't in your shoe locker?
Pardon?
Or have you ever experienced
having your gym clothes stolen?
No, I haven't.
Why do you ask?
I've had both happen to me.
I'm sure you don't understand,
but I was fat and had a bad personality,
so a lot of people hated me.
The few that got close to
me only did so because
Come on.
I was rich and they were looking for handouts.
So I know that you're different
from those guys back then.
But...
You don't actually like me, either.
Being this close, she can't hide
the mismatch between her
behavior and her fervor.
You can call me unfair,
but I don't want to go any further with
someone who's not actually serious.
Sorry...
I'll be taking this back.
You're going to choose Aki-sama.
Is that what you mean?
That's...
That's my...
My stomach hurts.
revenge.
I wonder if this is
the "heartbreak" I've heard others talk about.
Ah, Makabe-kun!
Over here!
Where were you, Masamune-kun?
You're late!
Sorry.
Actually, did you lose
some weight, Makabe-kun?
No, I'm sure you're just imagining it.
Sorry, I'm going to go refill my card.
Aki-sama?
I-It's nothing.
I guess the only one
missing is Fujinomiya-san.
Makabe-kun?
N-No, it's nothing.
So you guys did invite her.
Of course! We were talking about going
with everyone who went to the island.
This is awkward.
Maybe I should have canceled.
How am I even supposed to face her now?
But Fujinomiya-san is running pretty late.
She's not the type to be late.
Fujinomiya-san's not coming.
Huh?
She sent me an email this morning
saying she was canceling
because she wasn't feeling well.
I see. That's too bad.
So we might as well get going.
It's probably my fault, isn't it?
Sorry about that.
Huh? It's just you, Master?
Where's everyone else?
Futaba-san is in the bathroom.
And Adagaki?
Aki-sama is getting her fill of ice cream.
Because she couldn't eat it
properly with everyone around.
I see.
Pig's Foot, what happened?
Huh?
You're acting strange. Aki-sama, too.
What happened yesterday?
Er, I don't think anything happened.
I have a feeling Adagaki might've
gotten pissed at me, but...
Well, whatever.
Sorry about that. I left my
underwear in the locker.
Everyone's here. All right, let's go home!
Wh-What?
Makabe Masamune!
Huh? Shidou-san?
What did you do to Lady Neko-sama?!
What do you mean?
Lady Neko-sama has gone missing!
She's nowhere to be found!
She's missing? Since when?
President, you got an email
from her this morning, right?
Last night, when I called
from Kyoto, she was there.
When I came back in the
morning, her room was empty.
Oh, so it doesn't seem like
she's actually run away yet.
She left behind all her medication
that controls her seizures.
I can't see it as some normal outing.
Huh? Is she sick?
You fool! You were that close to her,
and you didn't even notice?
A normal person wouldn't
take so much medication.
Of course it's because she's sick!
S-Sorry, I didn't notice.
Blood?!
Multivitamin
Magnesium
Beer yeast and propolis.
This company's propolis has a patented method
for how it's absorbed into your body,
making it more effective.
Then there's the magnesium and...
That was all for real?
But why would she try to deceive me, then?
Wait...
She wanted me to be deceived?
She didn't want us to
think that she was weak,
so she created this façade of the
mysterious woman, Fujinomiya Neko,
who had a fake smile and manner of speaking,
and kept the truth hidden
behind smoke and mirrors?
So Fujinomiya-san's in a dangerous condition?
Yes. We must find her quickly.
So answer me truthfully.
What did you do to her?
Huh?
I know you came to the apartment
by yourself yesterday.
Yesterday?
What am I supposed to say?
Actually, now is the time
to say everything.
I declined.
I formally told her that
I couldn't go out with her.
Because I was going to choose Adagaki Aki.